export const questions =
    [
        {
            id: 1,
            question: "What are some of the major achievements in Cristiano Ronaldo's football career?",
            answer1: "Winning 10 FIFA World Cup titles",
            answer2: "Scoring over 800 career goals",
            answer3: "Being the highest goal-scorer in the UEFA Champions League",
            answer4: "Winning the Ballon d'Or 12 times",
            trueAnswer: "Being the highest goal-scorer in the UEFA Champions League",
            bgColor: "black",
            color: "white",
            colorcheck: "",
            isCheck: false
        },
        {
            id: 2,
            question: "How did Cristiano Ronaldo start his professional football career?",
            answer1: "At FC Barcelona",
            answer2: "At Sporting CP in Portugal",
            answer3: "At Real Madrid",
            answer4: "At Manchester United",
            trueAnswer: "At Sporting CP in Portugal",
            bgColor: "black",
            color: "white",
            colorcheck: "",
            isCheck: false

        },
        {
            id: 3,
            question: "What clubs has Cristiano Ronaldo played for, and what were his contributions to each?",
            answer1: "FC Barcelona, Bayern Munich, Manchester United, Real Madrid",
            answer2: "Sporting CP, Manchester United, Real Madrid, Juventus, Al-Nassr",
            answer3: "Chelsea, Paris Saint-Germain, Liverpool, Real Madrid",
            answer4: "Inter Milan, AC Milan, Real Madrid, Manchester United",
            trueAnswer: "Sporting CP, Manchester United, Real Madrid, Juventus, Al-Nassr",
            bgColor: "black",
            color: "white",
            colorcheck: "",
            isCheck: false

        },
        {
            id: 4,
            question: "How has Cristiano Ronaldo's playing style evolved over the years?",
            answer1: "He has always played as a defender",
            answer2: "He started as a midfielder and evolved into a forward",
            answer3: "He began as a goalkeeper and switched to a striker",
            answer4: "He has always been a central midfielder",
            trueAnswer: "He started as a midfielder and evolved into a forward",
            bgColor: "black",
            color: "white",
            colorcheck: "",
            isCheck: false

        },
        {
            id: 5,
            question: "What are some of the records held by Cristiano Ronaldo in club and international football?",
            answer1: "Most goals in a single Premier League season",
            answer2: "Most assists in FIFA World Cup history",
            answer3: "Most goals in the UEFA Champions League and most international goals by a European player",
            answer4: "Most yellow cards in La Liga history",
            trueAnswer: "Most goals in the UEFA Champions League and most international goals by a European player",
            bgColor: "black",
            color: "white",
            colorcheck: "",
            isCheck: false

        },
        {
            id: 6,
            question: "How has Cristiano Ronaldo influenced the game of football globally?",
            answer1: "By introducing the offside rule",
            answer2: "By revolutionizing football management",
            answer3: "By setting new standards in athleticism, professionalism, and global brand presence",
            answer4: "By changing the dimensions of the football field",
            trueAnswer: "By setting new standards in athleticism, professionalism, and global brand presence",
            bgColor: "black",
            color: "white",
            colorcheck: "",
            isCheck: false
        },
        {
            id: 7,
            question: "What are some of Cristiano Ronaldo's notable personal and professional rivalries?",
            answer1: "Rivalry with Neymar Jr. in Ligue 1",
            answer2: "Rivalry with Kylian Mbapp√© in Serie A",
            answer3: "Rivalry with Lionel Messi in La Liga and beyond",
            answer4: "Rivalry with Diego Maradona in the Premier League",
            trueAnswer: "Rivalry with Lionel Messi in La Liga and beyond",
            bgColor: "black",
            color: "white",
            colorcheck: "",
            isCheck: false
        },
        {
            id: 8,
            question: "How does Cristiano Ronaldo maintain his fitness and performance levels as an athlete?",
            answer1: "By training only once a week",
            answer2: "By following a strict diet, regular training, and personalized fitness routines",
            answer3: "By avoiding any form of exercise",
            answer4: "By focusing solely on yoga",
            trueAnswer: "By following a strict diet, regular training, and personalized fitness routines",
            bgColor: "black",
            color: "white",
            colorcheck: "",
            isCheck: false
        },
        {
            id: 9,
            question: "What philanthropic activities and charitable contributions has Cristiano Ronaldo been involved in?",
            answer1: "Funding the construction of new football stadiums",
            answer2: "Donating to children's hospitals, disaster relief efforts, and funding cancer research",
            answer3: "Investing solely in sports betting companies",
            answer4: "Donating all his earnings to his football clubs",
            trueAnswer: "Donating to children's hospitals, disaster relief efforts, and funding cancer research",
            bgColor: "black",
            color: "white",
            colorcheck: "",
            isCheck: false
        },
        {
            id: 10,
            question: "How has Cristiano Ronaldo's brand and marketability impacted his career and the sports industry?",
            answer1: "By staying completely out of public view",
            answer2: "By becoming one of the most marketable athletes, endorsing numerous brands, and launching his own product lines",
            answer3: "By avoiding all commercial endorsements",
            answer4: "By focusing only on local advertisements",
            trueAnswer: "By becoming one of the most marketable athletes, endorsing numerous brands, and launching his own product lines",
            bgColor: "black",
            color: "white",
            colorcheck: "",
            isCheck: false
        }

    ]